suppose your baggage or personal items
are permanently lost
stolen or damaged by your common carrier
which is to say
your airline hotel train or
transportation company
in that case the baggage loss benefit
reimburses you for the value of those
items
this can include your luggage clothing
and other personal items
there's usually a maximum payable amount
per item as well as
a coverage maximum typically ranging
between
two hundred fifty dollars to three
thousand dollars per person
the amount of coverage you receive will
depend on the plan you choose
additionally items like iphones laptops
and heirloom jewelry
are not usually covered so be sure to
read your plan limitations and
exclusions
see personal property pack or gadget
coverage if you're interested in
coverage for devices like your
smartphone or digital camera
documentation such as receipts are
required and it's important that the
carrier hotel or tour operator provide a
statement of loss
remember the cost and coverage of
insurance is specific to your policy
and can change based on the individual
making the purchase
this video acts as a helpful guide but
cannot guarantee coverage
always read the policy details and if
you need help with the fine print
call us we'll help answer any questions
you may have
also please note that nothing in this
video
is medical advice specific to you
you should not be making any decisions
on medical care or treatment options
based on this video this is only meant
to be educational
please see a qualified and licensed
medical professional
for any of those questions or concerns